

Details

Matru Pitru Chhaya, KVB Phadke Marg, Shivaji Chowk, Ghatkopar (w), Mumbai - 400086, India 9987256802 pragati123dandekar@gmail.com

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

26th September 1992 Mumbai

NATIONALITY Indian

Skills

Customer relations and communications

Internal and external Meeting arrangements

Creating meeting reports for Team Accountability

Microsoft Office 365

Mac OS

Languages

English

Marathi

Hindi

Profile

Experienced customer service associate and facility management professional. Highly motivated individual with exceptional delivery in carefully curated action plans, favourable vendor contracts and comprehensive regulations compliance. Trained and skilled at coping with fast-paced work environment and always being raring to go.

Employment History

Front Office Executive at Genius Consultants Limited (Amazon-Mumbai), Mumbai

OCTOBER 2022 — JULY 2023

- Oversaw office inventory activities by ordering and requisitions and stocking and shipment receiving.
- Scheduled meetings, coordinated with invitees and organized logistics, technology and refreshments for executive management and customers.
- Maintained office machines and equipment within budgets and contacted outside repair personnel to avoid productivity interruptions.
- Updated reports, managed accounts, and generated reports for company database.
- Assisted coworkers and staff members with special tasks on daily basis.
- Opened and properly distributed incoming mail to promote quicker response to client inquiries.
- Built and maintained excellent customer relationships through timely response to inquiries and going above and beyond to accommodate unusual requests.
- Interacted with vendors, contractors and professional services personnel to receive orders, direct activities, and communicate instructions.
- Managed filing system, entered data and completed other clerical tasks.

Customer Service Executive at InterGlobe Aviation Pvt Ltd (Indigo), Mumbai

JUNE 2019 — OCTOBER 2022

- Actively listened to customers, handled concerns quickly and escalated major issues to supervisor.
- Handled customer inquiries and suggestions courteously and professionally.
- To carry out safe and secure on time operations in accordance with the ground operations manual and all applicable procedures.
- Assist customers through all procedures related to arrivals departures in the following activities.

Reservations ticketing:

- · Making reservations across the counter
- · Selling of tickets.
- Remitting cash to the concerned department.

Departures

- Setting up of Check in counters.
- Maintain high quality of Check in procedures.
- · To assist customers with special requests.

Arrivals

- To assist customers with special requests.
- To assist customers with Mishandled / damaged baggage. Prepare all required reports for the same.
- Co-ordination with the baggage vendor for the damaged bags.
- Follow up with the en-route stations regarding lost baggage.

Senior Customer Service Assistant at Jet Airways Pvt Ltd, Mumbai

APRIL 2014 — MAY 2019

- Actively listened to customers, handled concerns quickly and escalated major issues to supervisor.
- Handled customer inquiries and suggestions courteously and professionally.
- To carry out safe and secure on time operations in accordance with the ground operations manual and all applicable procedures.
- Assist customers through all procedures related to arrivals departures in the following activities.

Reservations ticketing:

- Making reservations across the counter
- · Selling of tickets.
- · Remitting cash to the concerned department.

Departures

- Setting up of Check in counters.
- · Maintain high quality of Check in procedures.
- To assist customers with special requests.

Arrivals

- To assist customers with special requests.
- To assist customers with Mishandled / damaged baggage. Prepare all required reports for the same.
- Co-ordination with the baggage vendor for the damaged bags.
- Follow up with the en-route stations regarding lost baggage.

Junior Sales Executive at Strawberi Holidays Division of Kesari Tours Pvt Ltd, Mumbai

JUNE 2013 — MARCH 2014

- Primarily managed bookings and sales of Customized Domestic and International tour packages.
- Period of 9 months gave an in-depth understanding of travel and tourism around the globe.

Education

Bachelor of Commerce, Thakur College of Science And Commerce, Mumbai

JUNE 2010 — MAY 2013

Accountancy And Finance

Diploma in Aviation And Hospitality, Frankfinn Institute of Airhostess Training, Mumbai

MARCH 2010 — MARCH 2011

Aviation And Hospitality

Higher Secondary Education, Thakur College of Science And Commerce, Mumbai

JUNE 2008 — MARCH 2010

Higher Secondary Education with First Class

Senior Secondary Education, St. Lawrence High School, Mumbai

JUNE 2007 — MARCH 2008

Senior Secondary Education with First Class